carreg.co.uk 2016-10-13

# Car Reg Privacy Policy

## 1\. Online Privacy Practices

CarReg is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may have similar products and services we may be able to offer you.

## 2\. Subscription

In some areas of our website, we ask you to provide information as we may wish to reply to you after your visit. This would include where you subscribe to our newsletters or register to for alerts for an item we do not yet have in stock, or provide feedback to CarReg through an online contact form or when you complete any on line survey we may offer from time to time. When you do so, we ask you to give CarReg your name, email address and other personal information that will be needed to supply the services to you. In relation to any mailings you can ‘unsubscribe’ at any time. We may use your personal data for future email mailings, support, notification of new products available and releases, general correspondence regarding the products which may relate to your enquiry or order. If you would rather not receive future marketing emails from CarReg please inform us by email at [aftersales@carreg.co.uk](mailto:aftersales@carreg.co.uk?subject=No%20More%20Marketing%20Please).

The information you provide will be kept confidential and will be used only to support your customer relationship with us. We do not disclose or sell your information outside our companies group except if we sell the whole or part of our business at a future date.

## 3\. Trading/Website Security

Making sure you can buy safely and securely online is a priority for CarReg and we have made efforts to ensure that our security is one of our highest. We have devoted a great deal of effort to ensure that our online security measures help to safeguard your information. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Skypay are the payment gateway providers. We use industry-standard Thawte Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of:

  * Potentially sensitive information such as your name and address and telephone details
  * Critically-sensitive information like your payment card number

We hope that once you understand the measures we take to help ensure secure transactions and privacy, and the steps you can take yourself, you will be as happy about the safety of your online transaction and order information as we are. We have no desire to infringe your privacy while using our site and we will never provide your personal information to anyone else except if in future we sell our business in whole or in part.

## 4\. Cookies and How we use them

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

This Policy is effective from July 2012 and may be updated from time to time when necessary.
